Bees have barbed stingers that can stay in the skin and continue pumping venom.
If stung by a bee, you should act quickly to get that stinger out as soon as possible.
Instead of pinching it, it is better to use the edge of a credit card
to scrape the stinger away in the opposite direction from how it went in.
Once the stinger is removed, you'll want to wash the area thoroughly with soap and water
and apply an ice pack to help manage the pain and swelling.
While you provide this care, your most critical task is to monitor the person
for any signs of an allergic reaction.
If you notice immediate red flags like trouble breathing or swelling of the face and throat,
you should use an epinephrine auto-injector, if they have one prescribed,
and call 911 immediately.